Asta e povestea unui viitor posibil.
Au trecut zece ani, nu-i așa?
Stăpâne?
Ce este, Roxanne?
Ce facem aici?
Acest loc pare cât de poate de obișnuit.
Genul de sat agricol
pe care-l găsești oriunde.
Sau poate e o stațiune balneară?
Am venit aici în vacanță?
Nu, acest loc e un sat
complet obișnuit. Doar că...
am venit aici odată, acum mult timp.
Ce? Aici?
Da.
Înainte să te întâlnesc pe tine, Roxanne.
E un grajd.
E cumva special acest loc?
Da.
Just remembering what it was like.
I do feel nostalgic for this place,
but I don't remember it very well anymore.
Durandal
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
MP Absorption
Incantation Interruption
Hei, mă mai ții minte?
Sau ești un alt cal?
If so, the thief who stole those
sandals has nothing to worry about.
S-a întâmplat ceva?
Doar mă gândeam că părul lui are o culoare neobișnuită.
Te referi că are părul negru?
Nu prea vezi asta pe aici.
It's like yours.
Da, așa este.
IDENTIFICARE
MIO
<BĂIAT - 9 ani>
Nivel 1
Mio și Michio, nu?
Și vârsta se potrivește.
Ei bine...
Asta e ceea ce s-a întâmplat.
Ce plantezi?
Kyupiko.
Kyupiko, nu?
E specialitatea acestui sat, nu?
Părinții tăi o duc bine?
Mama, da.
Dar tatăl meu a murit
înainte să mă nasc.
Înțeleg. O asculți pe mama ta?
Da.
Bun.
INVENTAR
IDENTIFICARE
Scimitar of Rage
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
Dă-i această sabie mamei tale.
If she allows it, then it's yours.
Ce?
Folosește această sabie
ca să-ți protejezi mama.
Dar...
Nu fi timid.
Acum, ascultă.
Să ții acea sabie în mână
nu te face mai puternic.
Ci sabia e cea puternică.
Nu uita asta.
Bine.
Îți mulțumesc, domnule.
Domnule, nu?
Îmi cer scuze, Roxanne. Prima sabie pe care ți-o dădusem am lăsat-o în grija altcuiva.
Nu mă deranjează.
Cine era acel băiat?
Nu l-am mai întâlnit până acum.
Dar probabil îl cunosc pe tatăl acelui copil.
Să mergem.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Restaurantul
Vale, orașul Vale
Trezeci și trei de monede de aur înseamnă 330.000 de nari.
Îmi voi folosi monedele de argint ca să plătesc restul sumei,
ceea ce înseamnă că mai
am nevoie de 70.000 de nari.
Dacă e să-l cred pe negustorul de sclavi,
există două modalități
de a face bani repede.
Un labirint?
Da. A fost descoperit zilele trecute în pădurea de la vest.
Nu de asta ai venit în acest oraș?
Nu am venit aici intenționat.
Explorarea labirinturilor
e ceva ce fac aventurierii?
Da. La urma urmei, pot vinde toate obiectele pe care le obțin doborând demoni.
Pentru cei încrezători în abilitățile lor, labirinturile sunt o sursă de venit garantată.
Dar e dificil să obții o sumă mare de bani într-o perioadă scurtă de timp.
Deci vânătoarea de recompense ar fi o metodă mai rapidă.
Aduce bani frumoși,
dar nu o recomand.
De ce nu?
Deoarece bandiții preferă să scape de vânătorii de recompense.
Dacă atragi prea mult atenția...
Tu devii ținta.
Așa este.
În plus, deși e o metodă mai eficientă decât explorarea labirinturilor,
nu sunt multe recompense ce merită riscul.
Înțeleg.
Încă mai am cinci zile ca
s-o cumpăr pe Roxanne.
Voi încerca, mai întâi, metoda sigură.
Voi merge în acel labirint.
Dar, mai întâi, trebuie să mă ocup de asta.
Lupta cu acei bandiți a
făcut un lucru foarte clar.
Această sabie e incredibilă,
puțin cam prea mult.
Oamenii vor veni să mi-o ia,
SANDALE
exact cum am furat eu acele sandale.
S-a zis cu mine dacă rămân fără ea.
La urma urmei, am pus 63 de puncte bonus în chestia asta.
Reset Character.
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Weapon
●●●●●●
Accessories
○○○○○○
That should do it.
Și acum...
To acquire a suitable weapon
to replace Durandal.
Identify
Scimitar
No Skill
Identify
Scimitar
No Skill
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
●Empty
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
●Empty
Loc liber? Does that mean I
can add skills to it later?
Sir, is there something you're interested in?
Are all these scimitars the same price?
Yes.
Sounds like he doesn't know
about the empty skill slots.
Then, I'll buy this one.
Identify
Scimitar
Skill Slot
●Empty
Thank you.
I'm looking for some
protective equipment, too.
In that case, how about these?
Vale
Western Woods
I think he said the entrance was around here.
Adventurer
Explorer
Mage
If there are Mages,
Adventurer
Explorer
Knight
Warrior
Mage
then he must be using teleportation magic.
That's the entrance to the labyrinth?
I should head inside, too.
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
I'll remove my discount
skill and re-equip Durandal.
And then...
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
Okay. That should do it.
Whoa. It doesn't even feel
like I'm touching anything.
Come on, buck up.
Whoops.
So this is a labyrinth.
Vale Labyrinth
First Floor
Visibility's not very good, but it
doesn't seem like I'll need a light.
And it's surprisingly tidy.
But a labyrinth is a labyrinth.
I need to be prepared for monsters.
Job Settings.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Huh? I've got more jobs.
Explorer?
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
Come to think of it,
didn't I gain the Thief job
after stealing those sandals?
Status
Kaga Michio
<Male 17 Years Old>
Villager: Lv 1
Thief: Lv 1
Equipment: Sandals
Villager: Lv 1
Thief: Lv 1
Equipment: Sandals
Which means I acquired the Explorer
job by entering the labyrinth.
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
What's this?
Hero: Lv 1
Effects: Moderate HP Increase Moderate MP Increase
Moderate Strength Increase Moderate Endurance Increase
Moderate Intelligence Increase Moderate Spirit Increase
Moderate Dexterity Increase Moderate Agility Increase
Skills: Overwhelming
Hero? When did I get this?
It seems pretty useful.
I'll select this as my second job
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Villager: Lv 2
Thief: Lv 2
Hero: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
and Explorer as my third.
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
One of the Explorer's skills is Item Box...
Item Box
So this is the effect of the
Incantation Reduction skill.
Item Box
I don't know how it works,
but it seems convenient.
What else?
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Explorer: Lv 1
Effects: Minor Endurance Increase
Skills: Item Box Operation
Party Organization
Dungeon Walk
Dungeon Walk?
DESTINAȚIE
Destination?
That room I was in earlier, then.
Huh... This is convenient, too.
Dungeon Walk.
I'll head back outside next.
It's not called Dungeon Walk for nothing.
I can only choose destinations
inside labyrinths.
Which means that was some
other kind of spell.
Adventurer
Explorer
Mage
Then, I'll head back to that hall—
Destinations are limited
even within labyrinths, too?
There's so much I don't know.
This sucks.
Identify.
Needle Wood: Lv 1
Is that an enemy?
Time to see how far I can go.
One hit, huh?
This must be because of Durandal.
Branch
The needle wood dropped an item, huh?
I'm not sure what it is, but I'll take it.
Hey, there's another one.
Needle Wood: Lv 1
Come to think of it, the
Hero job had a skill, too.
I think it was...
Overwhelming.
The needle wood's movements slowed down?
No, am I moving faster?
Not that it matters either way.
Once I swing my sword up
through it, it'll be over.
But what good would that do?
Why am I even doing this?
Dazed
I'd rather wrap myself up in a futon and...
What was that?
I suddenly lost the will to do anything.
Wait a minute. I felt the same thing
after I used Dungeon Walk earlier.
This sucks.
I know! It's my MP!
Expending MP by casting spells dampens
my mood and makes me pessimistic.
I returned to normal immediately afterwards
because of Durandal's MP Absorption.
I may be able to recover my MP,
but repeatedly falling into a
depression isn't a fun time.
I shouldn't use too many
spells until I have more MP.
Is this where I sell items?
Yes.
In that case...
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
I'd like to sell these, please.
One moment, please.
Your total is 273 nars.
I see.
Restaurantul
Vale, orașul Vale
Two hundred seventy-three nars
for 21 branches.
Without the 30% increase,
that would've been ten nars per branch.
Supposing I kill ten in
an hour, that's 100 nars.
In ten hours, I'd earn 1,000 nars.
That's nowhere near close
enough to buy Roxanne.
I'll try staying in the
labyrinth longer tomorrow.
I guess I got up too early.
I can't even see where I'm standing.
Maybe I'll head back and get a lantern.
No, wait.
Come to think of it, in
my Bonus Incantations...
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Teleportare
This is it.
Teleport.
Etajul 1, Labirintul din Vale
All right, it worked.
Crap, it worked. Why did I
come to this dangerous place?
I didn't even want to come here.
Crap.
Reset Character
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
30% Sell Price Increase
Bonus Weapons
Incantation Reduction
Critical Strike Rate
I'm thinking negatively again.
I need to defeat an enemy
quickly so I can recover my MP.
I can't keep going.
I'd forgotten I don't have infinite health.
Anyway, it would take 700 hours to earn
70,000 nars at a rate of 100 nars per hour.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Equipped Jobs
Jobs
Sătean: Nivel 5
Explorator: Nivel 3
Hoț: Nivel 3
Erou: Nivel 2
1. Sătean: Nivel 5
2. Explorator: Nivel 3
3. Erou: Nivel 2
At least I've gained levels
thanks to my efforts.
Maybe I should go to a deeper
level of the dungeon after all.
A secret room?
What's that?
Could it be a treasure?
A broken sword?
No.
This isn't a secret treasure room.
It's a monster den.
Crap.
If I keep taking blows like that, I'll die.
I should leave for now.
Dungeon Walk.
I had a feeling it wouldn't
work during encounters.
If I can't run, I'll have to fight.
All right.
I can make up for the health loss
with Durandal's HP Absorption.
Overwhelming.
Crap, I'm low on MP.
I can't let them get behind me.
Overwhelming presumably consumes
a large amount of MP.
It'll take more than a couple
of monsters to recover it.
That said, if I'm too stingy with
my MP, then I'll slowly bleed out.
Overwhelming.
All right. I'm in the corner.
I can't get attacked from behind here.
This may be another world,
but it's still my reality.
Being defeated here would
certainly mean my death.
But I'll fight, even if it could kill me.
I thought I was gonna die.
No,
without Durandal's HP Absorption,
I definitely would've bit it.
That's enough for today.
What's that?
Poarta vestică a
castelului, orașul Vale
Did something happen?
Yeah, it's a bandit corpse.
Probably one of the bandits who
used to hang out in this town.
Used to?
You mean you don't know?
Recently a group of bandits left this town.
Nobody knows if they
moved their headquarters
because the knights started
cracking down on them
or they lost a dispute
with a rival organization.
The bandits who left were robbing
travelers and attacking nearby villages.
Oh, I know all about that.
Looks like they're back for revenge.
Revenge?
Hey, wait.
If they're the survivors of the bandit
gang that attacked that village,
then shouldn't they be getting revenge on me?
No, it's hard to imagine that's the case.
They'd be seeking revenge on whoever
made them leave town in the first place.
In other words, the knights
or their rival organization.
Either way, he's one unlucky bastard.
No doubt.
How do you know that's a dead bandit?
Take a look.
His left hand's been cut off.
His Intelligence Card didn't
appear right away when he died,
so they took his whole hand instead.
Ugh. Who's so desperate for a bounty
that they'd chop off a corpse's arm?
The bounty...
Bounties, huh?
S-a întâmplat ceva?
Nu, nimic.
Așa este.
Even if I keep going back into that labyrinth,
it's unlikely I'll make much money.
Dacă tot îmi risc viața,
I should choose whatever method
gets me closer to Roxanne.
Nu riști, nu câștigi.
Am rămas fără opțiuni.
Trebuie să vânez bandiți.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem